<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on SeamlessAcccess</title>
    <link>https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on SeamlessAcccess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Seamless?</title>
      <link>https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/who-is-seamless/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/who-is-seamless/</guid>
      <description>Here would be a short description of those who have implemented SeamlessAccess.org and a brief description of what they were hoping to accomplish. This page has a gallery of screen shots of implementations, and a list of those who have implemented so far. Perhaps use cases are highlighted.
Organizations that are implementing SeamlessAccess:
 SpringerNature - description TENET - description all of those committed to beta implementation  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The User Experience</title>
      <link>https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/how-it-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/how-it-works/</guid>
      <description>Here is a description of how the SeamlessAccess service works and what the user experience is like. There would need to be a bit more intro text so that it shows up correctly on the summary page.
Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a participating service</title>
      <link>https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/how-to-participate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/how-to-participate/</guid>
      <description>A description about the beta, the terms of service and the usage guidelines. Also information about responsibilities in using the service.
Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus. Memorata haberet sepulcrales gentisque dum sic, in flumina templa!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing the technology</title>
      <link>https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/implementing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/implementing/</guid>
      <description>Information about implementation including
 the three flavors of implementation Instructions for implementing the limited flavor Instructions for implementing the standard flavor Instructions for implementing the advanced flavor Button guidelines Handling errors Getting help  Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communicating SeamlessAccess</title>
      <link>https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/communication-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/communication-resources/</guid>
      <description>Information about communication resources including
 Promoting via SeamlessAccess.org Template verbiage Use of the SeamlessAccess Sample presentations Infographics  Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus. Memorata haberet sepulcrales gentisque dum sic, in flumina templa!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Resources</title>
      <link>https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/visual-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lpaglione.github.io/learn-hugo/work/visual-resources/</guid>
      <description>This section includes all of the resources you will need to implement the user interface components of SeamelessAccess including:
 SeamlessAccess Logos (really these should be provided at the CDN, and provided via link, not as an image. This approach will provide greater flexibility should the visuals need to change at some point) icon image for the “open door icon” including the URL to the CDN-hosted version of it font expectations, if any, including a CDN-hosted version of the font expected sizes for the icon and the button in pixels HEX codes for the expected colors to be used Reference to the use guidelines  NOTE: it would be best if these are HOSTED versions of these assets, i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>